Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Educational Material, 1952-2002; Series 2; 103 Linear Feet
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - The Abusive Parent: Lee's Story, 1984; Series 2; Includes a filmstrip and audio cassette tape soundtrack. (Box 3799, Folder 2)
    Contents stored in "Child Abuse and Neglect: The NEA Multimedia Training Program" with other files all under the same box number.
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - The Administrators' Perspective, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 29 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 5)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Deborah Wore Designer Jeans, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 28 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 6)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - A Dragon in My Closet, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 22 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 7)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - The Professional Team, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 37 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 8)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Profiles of Abusive and Neglectful Parents, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 53 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 9)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Published Materials, 1984; Series 2; Contains leader's guides, scripts, pamphlets, and manuals for multimedia program. (Box 3799, Folder 1)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Recognizing Child Abuse and Neglect, 1984; Series 2; Includes a filmstrip and audio cassette tape soundtrack. (Box 3799, Folder 3)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Resource Organizations, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 25 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 10)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Setting Up a Program, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 37 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 11)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Support Groups and Services, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 38 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 12)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - Talking with the Victim, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette, 29 minutes. (Box 3799, Folder 13)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect - A Victim Remembers, 1984; Series 2; Includes a filmstrip and audio cassette tape soundtrack. (Box 3799, Folder 4)
  - The Children of Kosovo, undated; Series 2 (Box 4635, Folder 8)
  - Cinderella is DEAD!, 1973; Series 2; Includes 2 33 1/3 vinyl records, 2 leader's manuals, and 2 filmstrips. (Box 3668, Folder 3)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3676, file 5. Two filmstrips.
  - City Driving, 1960; Series 2 (Box 3969, Folder 7)
  - Classroom Group Management, 1974; Series 2; Filmstrip with 12" vinyl record soundtrack, audio cassette soundtrack, and discussion guide. (Box 3668, Folder 9)
  - Cluster Report, undated; Series 2; 16 mm color film, 15:00. (Box 3798, Folder 7)
  - CNN "Inside Politics" Bob Dole Resigns Entire Program, May 15, 1996; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3964, Folder 7)
  - The Coming Breakthrough in Education, undated; series 2 (Box 4522, Folder 1)
  - Conference Time for Teachers and Parents, 1970; Series 2; Includes 2 33 1/3 vinyl records, 3 filmstrips, and leader's manuals. (Box 3668, Folder 4)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3676: 3 filmstrips.
  - Conn. Education Association/Uniserv "Arbitration Training: Evidence", April 12, 1994; Series 2; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 25)
  - Controlling Classroom Misbehavior, 1969; Series 2; Filmstrip with 12" vinyl record soundtrack, audio cassette tape soundtrack, and discussion guide. (Box 3668, Folder 8)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3834: four filmstrips.
  - Cooperative and Student Team Learning, 1989; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette tape soundtrack. (Box 3844, Folder 4)
  - Copying: Rights and Copyright, 1978; Series 2; Audio cassette soundtrack to filmstrip. Filmstrip was not present upon receipt at archives. (Box 3686, Folder 5)
  - Copying: Rights & Copyrights, 1979; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3835, Folder 3)
  - Counting Experiences: A Multimedia Program, 1978; Series 2; Contains two filmstrips with audio cassette soundtracks, one stand-alone filmstrip with teaching aid, one stand-alone audio cassette, and discussion guide. (Box 3853, Folder 4)
  - Creando una Formula para Obtener el Exito en las Escuelas de Bajo Rendimiento, May 17, 2001; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3996, Folder 6)
  - Creativity: A Way of Learning - Sound Filmstrip Stock No. 387-11618, 1973; Series 2; 2 33 1/3 LP Audible signal for manual equipment (Box 3662, Folder 13)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3666 File 8 2 Filmstrips
  - Critical Issues General Session - Danny Kaye & C. Heckler - Looped Master, July 1975; Series 2; Kaye, Danny; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3698, Folder 4)
  - David and Myra Sadker present Analyzing Teaching: Three Scenes from the Classroom, undated; Series 2; BETCAM video tape (Box 4058, Folder 25)
  - Deborah Wore Designer Jeans, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape. 28 minutes, with overview sheet. (Box 3803, Folder 4)
  - Deciding What to Teach Planning and Organizing For Teaching, 1964; Series 2; 2 33 1/3 rpm 18 Minutes Long Playing Inaudible 30/50 Cycle Signal For Use with Automatic Equipment (Box 3662, Folder 14)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3676 File 1 4 Filmstrips
  - Directions for the Future - DESP - NEA, Undated; Series 2; 33 1/3 rpm Directions For the Future by the Department of Elementary School Principals (Box 3662, Folder 15)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3666 File 9 Filmstrip
  - Discipline and Motivation: A Genuine Partnership, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 30 minutes, with discussion guide. (Box 4032, Folder 2)
  - Discipline and Motivation: A Genuine Partnership, 1978; Series 2; audio cassette tape (Box 4032, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Joy Elmer Morgan's Address to Retired NEA Staff, May 17, 1978; Series 2; Morgan, Joy Elmer; Audio cassette. (Box 3682, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Wigren - 2/5/73 KBPS, Portland, Ore, February 5, 1973; Series 2; Wigren, Harold E.; Audio cassette. (Box 3682, Folder 31)
  - A Dragon in My Closet - Cynthia Tower, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 22 minutes, with overview sheet. (Box 3804, Folder 2)
  - Driver Education Film Series, General Motors Presents "Driving Economically", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 8)
  - Driver Education Film Series, General Motors Presents, "Your Permit to Drive", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 9)
  - Educating Gifted and Talented Students - Printed Materials, 1980; Series 2; Includes filmstrip guides, lesson planning books, duplicating masters. (Box 3830, Folder 1)
    Contents stored in "Educating Gifted and Talented Students" with all other files under same box number.
  - Educating Gifted and Talented Students: Students and Teachers Together, 1980; Series 2; Contents stored in "Educating Gifted and Talented Students" with all other files under same box number.; Contains two filmstrips (First of three is not present); three soundtrack audiocassettes. (Box 3830, Folder 2)
  - Educating Gifted and Talented Students: Talks With Teachers About Gifted and Talented Students, 1980; Series 2; Includes four audio cassette tapes and discussion guide. (Box 3830, Folder 3)
  - Education, Limited (Show Reel), undated; Series 2; 1/4" magnetic audio tape on 12" reel. (Box 3853, Folder 3)
  - Education Programs for Southeast Asian Refugees. Don I. Wortman, 1976; Series 2; Audio cassette. (Box 3704, Folder 3)
  - EFC - Hubert Humphrey, undated; Series 2; Humphrey, Hubert H.; Magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3688, Folder 8)
  - Effective Teaching & the Cooperative Classroom: Games Students (and Teachers) Play - Alfred S. Alschuler, 1984; Series 2; Audio cassette with accompanying outline for Social Literacy Workshop. 2 copies. (Box 3704, Folder 5)
  - The Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965: A Sound Filmstrip, ca. 1965; Series 2; Contains filmstrip and vinyl record. (Box 3677, Folder 1)
    Contains separated materials in box 3678
  - Elements of the Learning Process, 1974; Series 2; Two filmstrips; two 33 1/3 vinyl records. (Box 3680, Folder 4)
    Contains spearated materials found in box 3681: two filmstrips.
  - Environmental Crisis: What the Individual Can Do, 1970; Series 2; Filmstrip; 33 1/3 vinyl record, approximately 17 minutes long. (Box 3680, Folder 5)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3681: filmstrip.
  - Evaluating Student Thinking Skills, 1987; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3844, Folder 5)
    Contains separated materials in box 3837: filmstrip.
  - "Facultymess" Seminar, 1998 (Box 4033, Cassette data_value_missing_4461df973a966b81cfe042edfda0ef8d)
  - Fire in Their Learning, 1954; series 2 (Box 4519, Folder 1)
  - Fighting For You, Your Schools, Your Student!, Undated; Series 2 (Box 4933, Folder 9)
  - Focus on Issues: Interview with John Ryor 1/5/78, January 6, 1978; Series 2; Ryor, John; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS, 22:04 min. (Box 3717, Folder 1)
  - Focus on the Individual - A Leadership Responsibility, 1965; Series 2; 33 1/3 RPM Long Playing Audible Signal Part I 18 minutes Part II 12 Minutes (Box 3672, Folder 14)
    Separated materials found in Box 3673 File 5 Filmstrip
  - Focus on Quality Inspection, 1961; Series 2; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS, 28 minutes. Soundtrack and script to filmstrip. Filmstrip is not included. (Box 3741, Folder 4)
  - Ford Motor Company, "Pedestrians", 1956; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 10)
  - Ford Motor Company #1, "Care of the Car", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 11)
  - Ford Motor Company #2, "Driving at Night", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 12)
  - Ford Motor Company #3, "Driving in the City", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 13)
  - Ford Motor Company #5, "Driving under Adverse Conditions", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 14)
  - Ford Motor Company #6, "Parking the Car", undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 15)
  - Getting Credit - Banking Services, Undated; Series 2; Pre-Recorded Program Film 3 3/4 IPS 33 1/2 LP Microgroove (Box 3667, Folder 5)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3666 File 4
  - Gloria: Public Service Spot, Undated; Series 2; 16 mm sound color film. (Box 3720, Folder 1)
  - Good Pictures Can Tell Your Story, 1977; Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette. (Box 3677, Folder 4)
    Contains separated material found in box 3678: filmstrip.
  - GR Mock Debate Pre-Focus Group, June 12, 2000; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3977, Folder 1)
  - Grant Writing, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3965, Folder 5)
  - The Great Adventure #1 - CBS Affiliate Relations, SN631113, ca. 1963; Series 2; 16mm b/w film with audio track. (Box 3771, Folder 11)
  - Guidelines for Decision - On Issues In Elementary Education, 1961; Series 2; 33 1/3 rpm Long Play Guidelines for Decision by the Department of Elementary School Principals GRC-6540 (Box 3662, Folder 8)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3664 File 4 Filmstrip
  - The Handicapped, The Teachers, and the Law, ca. 1975; Series 2; Filmstrip, no audio soundtrack present. (Box 3676, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii State Teachers Association - Blueprint for Education (General Public Version), March 18, 2002; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3996, Folder 7)
  - HCR "Women's Leadership Training Program", March 4, 1991; Series 2; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 26)
  - Health Information Network H.I.V. Training Segment (5) - On The Street Interviews, Undated; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3965, Folder 10)
  - Helping Your Child in School, 1979; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3835, Folder 4)
  - Heritage and Horizon: Teaching Ideas for the Bicentennial - Filmstrip, Cassette tape, Script, Units Plans, Stock No. 1956-3-00, 1975; Series 2; Audio cassette tape (Box 3665, Folder 2)
    Separated materials found in Box 3664 File 3 Filmstrip
  - Highway Driving, 1960; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3969, Folder 16)
  - HIM HIV Training Program (5 Segments) - Segment 4: People with AIDS, June 10, 1992; Series 2; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 18)
  - Historical Highlights in the Education of Black Americans, Undated; Series 2; 33 1/3 LP Time: 23 Min. Audible Signal for manual equipment (Box 3662, Folder 9)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3664 FIle 5 Filmstrip
  - Homework: Effective Techniques, 1986; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette tape soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3844, Folder 6)
  - How Good is Your Child's School? - Sound Filmstrip - Stock No. 388-11930, 1967; Series 2; 33 1/3 LP Time appx. 14 mins. Audible signal for manual equipment (Box 3662, Folder 10)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3664 File 6 Filmstrip
  - How Teachers Can Work with Learning Disabled Students - III: "Teaching LD Adolescents;" IV: "Helping Teachers Teach the LD Student", 1978; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 22 minutes, with discussion sheet. (Box 3804, Folder 3)
  - How To Help Your Child Grow Up, 1974; Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette. (Box 3677, Folder 5)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3678: filmstrip.
  - How to Listen to Your Child - How to get Your Child to Listen to You, 1971; Series 2; 2 33 1/3 LP Time Aprrox. 10 Mins. Inaudible Signal For Automatic Equipment (Box 3662, Folder 7)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3664 File 1 2 Filmstrips
  - How You can Help Your Child Get the Most Out of School, 1968; Series 2; Two filmstrips; two 33 1/3 vinyl records, approximately 22 minutes long. (Box 3677, Folder 11)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3678.
  - How You Can Help Your Child Get the Most Out of School, 1968; Series 2 (Box 3835, Folder 5)
  - Humanizing Instruction (L. Wendell Rivers), 1974; Series 2; Audio cassette, 28 minutes. (Box 3682, Folder 35)
  - Hungry Children, 1983; Series 2; Audio cassette tape with discussion guide. (Box 3850, Folder 2)
  - I Am a Child, September 28, 1998; Series 2 (Box 4635, Folder 9)
  - Idaho Centennial Sub-Master (Pioneer Schools), undated; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 4022, Folder 3)
  - Identifying Student Thinking Skills, 1986; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3845, Folder 1)
  - Independent Reading - Maryann Murphy Manning and Gary L. Manning, 1983; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 30 minutes, with discussion guide. (Box 3804, Folder 4)
  - Influencing the Future: The NEA Teaching and Learning Tech. Exhibit, June 24, 1996; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3975, Folder 8)
  - Influential Americans Part 1, undated; Series 2; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 17)
  - Integrating Handicapped Students Into Regular Classrooms, 1979; Series 2; Two-part filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3845, Folder 2)
    Contains separated materials in box 3837: two filmstrips.
  - Interview Skills for Teachers, 1976; Series 2; Audio cassette tape and printed training manual. (Box 3851, Folder 2)
  - Introduction to P21 Skills, June 2006; Series 2; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 15)
  - Involving At-Risk Student in Learning, 1989; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3845, Folder 3)
  - It's Up To Congress, 1959; Series 2; 16mm black and white film, 21:00. (Box 3798, Folder 2)
  - It's Up To Congress (Transferred), 1959; Series 2; 16 mm black and white film, 21:00. (Box 3798, Folder 3)
  - It's Your Right: The Law Says...-Sound Filmstrip Stock: 388-11984, 1971-1972; Series 2; 33 1/3 LP Audible signal for manual equipment Audio cassette (Box 3662, Folder 1)
    Separated materials found in Box 3661 FIle 1 Filmstrip
  - The Labels and Reinforcement of Sex Role Stereotyping - Sound Filmstrip Stock No. 0572-4-00, 1973; Series 2; Part I The Labels: Feminity and Masculinity Part II The Reinforcement: Home, School, Community 33 1/3 LP Inaudible signal for automatic equipment (Box 3662, Folder 6)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3661 File 10 2 Filmstrips
  - Jane Ann Razeghl & Warren R. Johnson (Sex Education of the Handicapped: Preparing Teachers), circa 1978; Series 2; Audio cassette tape (Box 4031, Folder 15)
  - John Ryor on Department of Education - Positive Statement, Undated; Series 2; Ryor, John; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no indicated speed. (Box 3717, Folder 9)
  - Joshua In A Box, undated; Series 2; VHS cassette. (Box 3843, Folder 10)
  - Keys 2.0- Keys to Excellence for Your Schools, Undated; Series 2; CD-ROM (Box 4015, Folder 16)
  - Leadership Development - Narrator: Ralph Joy. Issue Organizing. Opening Statement, undated; Series 2; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 46)
  - Leadership Development - Narrator: Ralph Joy. Thinking Organizationally. Opening and Closing Statement., undated; Series 2; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 47)
  - Leading Question - August 28, 1959 - Sec. Fleming, Series 2; 1/4" magnetic audio tape on 12" reel. (Box 3853, Folder 2)
  - Learning Disabilities: Suggestions for Teaching, 1978; Series 2; Two audio cassettes, 25 minutes and 22 minutes, and discussion guide. (Box 3804, Folder 5)
  - Learning Disabilities eduPak, 1978-1979; Series 2; Includes two filmstrips, six audio cassettes, and assorted published materials. (Box 3833, Folder 1)
    Contains two-part filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack, "Integrating Handicapped Students into Regular Classrooms;" four-part audio-cassette program; discussion manuals; and seven-part booklet series on teaching subjects to handicapped students.
  - Learning Labs: Short Version, November, 1989; Series 2 (Box 3966, Folder 8)
  - Learning Labs Site Reports, undated; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 4022, Folder 4)
  - The Learning Process - Revised Edition, 1984; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette tape soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3845, Folder 5)
    Contains separated material in box 3848: four filmstrips.
  - Learning to Read, undated; series 2 (Box 4517, Folder 1)
  - Learning to Read, undated; series 2 (Box 4547, Folder 1)
  - Legacy of Honor/The Negro in American History, 1967-1968; Series 2; Filmstrip; 33 1/3 RPM vinyl record. (Box 3677, Folder 9)
    Contains separated materials found in box 3678: two filmstrips.
  - Legal Aspects of Teacher Strikes - Office of General Council, undated; Series 2; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 3 3/4 IPS. (Box 3771, Folder 10)
  - The Line to Progress, 1963; Series 2; Scotch recording Tape "The Line to Progress" 14 min. 7 1/2 ips DCT-NEA Pre-Recorded Program "The Line to Progress" 14 min. 7 1/2 ips DCT-NEA No beeps
    Separated materials found in Box 3664 File 8
  - Listening: From Sound to Meaning - Sound Filmstrip Stock No. 387-11616, 1972; Series 2; Listening: From Sound to Meaning 33 1/3 LP Time 10 1/2 Mins. Inaudible signal for Automatic equipment. (Box 3662, Folder 5)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3661 File 9 2 Filmstrips
  - Looking at Values, 1976; Series 2; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack, additional audiocassette introduction, and script/discussion guide. (Box 3852, Folder 2)
    Contains separated materials in box 3849/5: filmstrip.
  - Looking at Values - Filmstrip, Casette Tapes, Script, Stock No. 0710-7, 1976; Series 2; 3 Audio cassette tapes (Box 3663, Folder 6)
    Separated materials found in Box 3661 File 8 Filmstrip
  - Making Schools Safe 1, September 18, 1992; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 4022, Folder 5)
  - Making Schools Safe 2, undated; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 4022, Folder 6)
  - Man and His Environment: A New Approach to Environmental Education, 1970; Series 2; Filmstrip; 33 1/3 vinyl record, approximately 14 minutes long. (Box 3680, Folder 1)
  - Man and His Environment: A New Approach to Environmental Education (with Guide), 1970; Series 2; Filmstrip with 33 1/3 vinyl record soundtrack and discussion guide. (Box 3853, Folder 1)
    Contains separated material in box 3849/9: filmstrip.
  - Mathematics for Tomorrow, undated; series 2 (Box 4532, Folder 1)
  - A Matter of Equity, June 21, 1985; Series 2; Two copies of VHS videocassette, 20 min. (Box 3828, Folder 9)
  - Media Programs for Individual Schools - Filmstrip, 7 1/2 IPS Taped narration - Guide and Script, 1969; Series 2; Media Programs for Individual Schools. 7 1/2 IPS 10 Minutes. (Box 3663, Folder 5)
    Separated materials found in Box 3661 File 7 Filmstrip
  - A Message to State Association Executive from Don Cameron, NEA Exectuive Director, September 9, 1992; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3996, Folder 8)
  - Mike Makes His Mark, March 1987; Series 2; VHS videocassette, 20 min. (Box 3828, Folder 4)
  - More Than We Bargained For: A Local on the Move [1 of 2], undated; Series 2; 119 slides. Audio cassette soundtrack in file 2. (Box 3844, Folder 1)
    Montgomery County Education Association
  - More Than We Bargained For: A Local on the Move [2 of 2], undated; Series 2; Audio cassette soundtrack to slideshow in file 1. (Box 3844, Folder 2)
  - Motivation and Adolescents, 1978; Series 2; Audio cassette tape, 20 minutes; discussion guide. (Box 3704, Folder 6)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Classroom Climate and Student Motivation, Series 2; Filmstrip, audio cassette 5:30 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 7)
    Contents stored in "Motivation in Learning: A Multimedia Program" with other files all under the same box number.
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Discipline and Motivation: A Genuine Partnership, Series 2; Audio cassette, approximately 15 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 3)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Disequilibrium as a Motivating Factor, Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette 5:45 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 11)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - The Five Myths of Motivation, Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette, approximately 6 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 8)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Motivation and Adolescents, Series 2; Audio cassette, 20 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 2)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - The Need for Self-Actualization, Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette 5:45 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 10)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Progress and Mastery as a Factor in Continuing Motivation, Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette 5:30 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 13)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Published Materials, 1977-1978; Series 2; Contains guidebooks and pamphlets. (Box 3679, Folder 1)
  - Motivation In Learning 1978 - Student Attitude Toward the Teacher, Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette 4:45 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 9)
  - Motivation in Learning 1978 - Tape 1: What is Motivation?/Tape 2: The Time Continuum Model of Motivation, Series 2; Audio cassette, approximately 23 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 4)
  - Motivation in Learning 1978 - Tape 3: Student Attitude Toward the Subject and Learning Situation/Tape 4: Fear and Anciety Related to Motivation, Series 2; Audio cassette, approximately 24 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 5)
  - Motivation in Learning 1978 - Tape 5: Stimulation Value of Teacher Inquiry/Tape 6: Interest and Involvement, Series 2; Audio cassette, approximately 23 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 6)
  - Motivation in Learning 1978 - Tape 7: Feelings Relative to Student Motivation/Tape 8: Responsibility and Learning, Series 2; Audio cassette, approximately 23 minutes long. (Box 3679, Folder 7)
  - Motivation In Learning 1983 - Classroom Climate and Student Motivation, 1978; Series 2; Filmstrip, audio cassette 5:30 minutes long. (Box 3800, Folder 11)
  - Motivation In Learning 1983 - Disequilibrium as a Motivating Factor, 1978; Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette 5:45 minutes long (Box 3800, Folder 2)
  - Motivation In Learning 1983 - The Five Myths of Motivation, 1978; Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette, approximately 6 minutes long. (Box 3800, Folder 3)
  - Motivation In Learning 1983 - The Need for Self-Actualization, 1978; Series 2; Filmstrip; audio cassette 5:45 minutes long. (Box 3800, Folder 4)